Now that we've learned more about what disaster recovery is overall,
现在我们已经了解到灾难恢复的总体情况
how do we do it in AWS?
我们如何在 AWS中做呢
What tools and services are at our disposal that will help us?
我们可以使用哪些工具和服务来帮助我们?
Geographic recovery.
地理恢复
Disaster recovery plans are intended to cover major service disruptions.
灾难恢复计划旨在覆盖主要服务中断
As such, a typical DR plan calls for re-establishing your platform a
因此 典型的 DR 计划需要重新建立您的平台
minimum of hundreds of miles away into multi-region services.
至少有  英里远进入多区域服务
If you need to prepare to be able to move hundreds of miles in AWS,
如果你需要准备在 AWS上移动几英里
this means you need to be able to move regions.
这意味着您需要能够移动区域
If you are running active,
如果您正在运行活动
active in multiple regions, excellent, you're done.
活跃在多个区域 优秀 您完成了
However, as we've discussed,
但是我们讨论过
the ease of running active,
活动的轻松
active in multiple regions depends a lot on the services that you utilize.
活动在多个区域中取决于您使用的服务
We've already seen how DynamoDB and S3 can be made multi-region with relative ease.
我们已经看到 DynamoDB 和 S3 如何能够以相对轻松的方式实现多区域
Some global services such as IAM,
一些全球服务 如 IAM
a multi-region by default,
缺省情况下为多区域
while others like CloudFront can be made multi-region.
而像 CloudFront 这样的其他则可以成为多区域
CloudFront takes your content from your source
CloudFront 从源获取内容
and distributes it from multiple regions around the world.
并将其分布于世界各地的多个地区
In this sense, it is always multi-region.
在这个意义上 它总是多区域的
However, by default, the source of your content,
但是缺省情况下 内容的来源
your origin Cloudfront terms,
您的原始 Cloudfront 术语
is only in one region and if that region fails,
只有一个地区如果那个地区失败了
your application is down.
您的应用程序已关闭
With CloudFront origin groups,
使用 CloudFront 源组
you can define multiple S3 buckets in multiple regions as failover buckets.
您可以在多个区域中定义多个 S3 存储区作为故障转移存储区
If CloudFront is no longer able to get your content from the primary bucket,
如果 CloudFront 不再能够从主存储区获取您的内容
it will then try a backup bucket.
然后 它将尝试备份存储区
Using this option, your CloudFront distribution can now survive a region failure.
使用此选项 您的 CloudFront 分布现在可以在区域故障中生存
DynamoDB can run in an active,
" 发电机 " 可以在活动的情况下运行
active scenario with fairly low cost and effort.
使用成本和工作量相当低的活动场景
RDS can create cross-region read replicas.
RDS 可以创建跨区域读副本
These keep current data in another region,
这些数据保存在另一个区域
but there will still be work to do to make that data usable as an active database.
但仍有工作要做 以将该数据用作活动数据库
You'll need to promote the read replica and then
你需要推广读副本然后
point your application at this new database instance.
将应用程序指向此新数据库实例
CloudFront can use multiple S3 buckets as
CloudFront 可以将多个 S3 存储区用作
the origin for the same assets and automatically failover between them.
相同资产的来源并自动在它们之间进行故障转移
Origin groups within CloudFront can use S3 buckets in
CloudFront 中的源组可以使用 S3 存储区
different regions and failover when necessary without manual intervention.
不同区域和故障转移 无需人工干预
S3 buckets can be automatically replicated across regions.
S3 存储区可以在跨区域自动复制
This provides a mechanism to keep current copies of S3 objects.
这提供了一种保持 S3 对象的当前副本的机制
You do then pay double for storing these objects,
你要付双倍的钱储存这些物品
but that is the cost of being prepared for DR incident
但这就是为 DR 事件做好准备的代价